<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CSCT Conference 2019 : Flow</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CSCT Conference 2019 : Flow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:36:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Venue</title>
      <link>http://example.org/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/venue/</guid>
      <description>Venue 2019 This year the Arnolfini plays host to the CSCT Conference, a hub for contemporary art and creativity.


Arnolfini is located in the centre of Bristol on Narrow Quay, between the harbourside and Prince Street.



Address
16 Narrow Quay
Bristol
BS1 4QA

On Foot From the south, cross the swing bridge from Prince Street. From the north or centre of the city, walk along the quayside leaving the centre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Centre and Groups</title>
      <link>http://example.org/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/research/</guid>
      <description>Research Centre and Groups The Computer Science and Creative Technologies Conference 2019 is hosted by a collection of its constituting research centres and groups from The University of the West of England. Computer Science Research Centre The Computer Science Research Centre (CSRC) is comprised of active researchers based at UWE, covering a range of disciplines across the field of computer science. The CSRC groups these areas into the following core themes which reflect the work of many of its members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special</title>
      <link>http://example.org/special/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/special/</guid>
      <description>Special Performance We are anouncing a very special performance soon&amp;hellip; Check back or follow UWE&amp;rsquo;s CSCT twitter for updates:
Follow @UWE_CSCT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program</title>
      <link>http://example.org/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/program/</guid>
      <description>Flow - 2019  Time Presenter Title Type Length   09:45 Tim Brailsford (HoD) Welcome Opening 15 minutes   10:00 Rebecca Fiebrink Using Data and Machine Learning to Support Human Creative Practices Keynote 50 minutes   Session 1       10:50 Chris Nash Musical Platforms: Patterns and Chaos in Music Talk 1 20 minutes   11:10 Frazer Barnes Printed sensors and how they will revolutionize the food supply chain and reduce waste Talk 2 20 minutes   11:30 Break Break Break 30 minutes   Session 2       12:00 Kevin Doyle Institute of Coding Highlight 15 minutes   12:15 Phil Legg, Jim Smith, and Richard Preen HASTE - Human-centric active-learning for decision support in threat exploration Talk 3 20 minutes   12:35 Tom Mitchell Interactive Sonification of Molecular Physics (Isomorph): Making the Invisible Audible Talk 4 20 minutes   13:00 Lunch Lunch Lunch 60 minutes   13:00 Ben G and Steve Battle Programming with potatoes Workshop 60 minutes   13:00 Multiple Posters Posters 60 minutes   14:15 Teresa Dillon In Your Aerial Keynote 45 minutes   Session 3       15:00 Dom Brown Designing an Immersive Musical Experience in Virtual Reality Talk 4 20 minutes   15:20 Luke Reed Immersive Audio in Cinematic VR Talk 6 20 minutes   15:40 Liz Lane  Performance 1 20 minutes   16:00 Break Break Break 60 minutes   17:00 Imogen Heap Performance 2 Performance 60 minutes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>http://example.org/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/registration/</guid>
      <description>Registration Follow @UWE_CSCT -- To register click here or fill out the form below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AGoodOne</title>
      <link>http://example.org/talks/agoodone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 17:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/talks/agoodone/</guid>
      <description>Great</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynotes</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 16:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keynotes/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Rebecca Fiebrink 
Dr Rebecca Fiebrink is currently a Senior Lecturer in Computing at Goldsmiths, University of London. She is the original creator of Wekinator, an open source software project that allows users to build new interactive systems by demonstrating human actions and matching them to computer responses, instead of writing code.
Accompanied by her students and research assistants, Fiebrink works on projects that develop technologies that enable new forms of human expression, creativity, and embodied interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>